a1vbcode.com 2012-10-03

# Visual Basic Code , VB.NET Code

| ASP.NET Web Hosting   
---  
[• 3 Months FREE  
• ASP.NET 4  
• MS SQL 2008  
• CLICK HERE!](http://www.discountasp.net/)   
   
Code   
  All  
  VB  
  VB.NET  
  ASP  
  ASP.NET  
  Snippets  
  Popular  
Resources   
  Submit Code  
  Forums  
  Articles  
  Tips  
  Links  
  Books  
  Contest  
  Mailing List  
  Link to us  
Product Spotlight   
Sponsor   
  **Privacy Statement**

**A1VBCode** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ A1VBCode ](http://www.a1vbcode.com/)

**Cookies**

Our Site uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. Cookies are used in the VB Forums section of this web site. These cookies are used to save user ID and passwords to simplify the posting of messages to the forums. 

We also use third party advertisements on our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

DoubleClick DART cookies  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx 

**Advertisers**

A1VBCode uses third-party advertising companies Google Adsense, BurstMedia, TribalFusion, and Valueclick to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit, <http://tribalfusion.com/TribalFusion/privacy.html>,  
<http://www.burstmedia.com/privacy.asp>,  
<http://www.valueclickmedia.com/privacy.shtml>, and  
<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>. 

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit   [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

**Registration Forms**

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email). 

Contact information from the registration forms is used to send information about our web site. The user's contact information is also used to get in touch with the user when necessary. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

**Contests**

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like email address). 

Contact information from the contests is used to ship prizes. The visitor's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

**External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. **A1VBCode** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Public Forums**

This site makes forums available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving newsletter/promotional information from us. 

  1. You can send email to [ feedback@a1vbcode.com ](mailto:feedback@a1vbcode.com)

**Data Quality/Access**

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  1. You can send email to [ feedback@a1vbcode.com ](mailto:feedback@a1vbcode.com)

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:   

|  | ASP.NET 2.0 Hosting   
---  
Sponsor
